University of Connecticut, Center for Oral History Interviews Collection 1984.0025
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Voices From The Second World War: An Oral History, 1999-2000 (Box 75, Box 74)
  - James Fontanna(54 pp.)
  - Arthur Frechette(51 pp.)
  - Delores Hammon(29 pp.)
  - Allen Hutchinson (28 pp.)
  - Moo Soo Hwang (82 pp.)
  - Franklin E. Johnson(77 pp.)
  - Peter O. Kliem (44 pp.)
  - Richard E. Kyte (41 pp.)
  - Edward Landeau (22 pp.)
  - Charles Lanham(36 pp.)
  - Edward Lapointe(68 pp.)
  - Clayton Lathrop(21 pp.)
  - Albert O. Montambault(24 pp.)
  - Barbara F. Palmer(45 pp.)
  - Dr. James S. Peters II (69 pp.)
  - Esther M. Phelps(24 pp.)
  - Alexander Roesell (57 pp.)
  - Caroline San Angelo(16 pp.)
  - Charles Theriault(54 pp.)
  - Harry Thies(53 pp.)
  - Bertram Wilson(30 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_650ef39090be22ff24b6590a673d50e3)
- Voices Of American Homemakers, 1981-1985 (Box 73)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Eleanor Arnold. Interviews By: Various. This project has been deposited in each of the fifty states. The Center for Oral History is the designated archive for Connecticut. Index to the collection is shelved with the Center for Oral History Interviews.]
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_6d902e984f9483c3955964f4e932e64f)
- Witnesses To Nuremberg, An Oral History Of American Participants At The War Crimes Trials, 1995-1996
  - Burson, Harold (32pp.), 1995 July 19; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Burson/Box79:1 (Box 79, Folder 1 [39153030525648])
  - Carlow, Burton (52 pp.), 1995 August 23; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Carlow/Box79:2 (Box 79, Folder 2 [39153030525655])
  - Ferencz, Benjamin (69 pp.), 1995 October 16; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Ferencz_B/Box79:4 (Box 79, Folder 4 [39153030525671])
  - Ferencz, Gertrude (32 pp.), 1995 October 16; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Ferencz_G/Box79:3 (Box 79, Folder 3 [39153030525663])
  - Fiss, Harry (48 pp.), 1995 July 11; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Fiss/Box79:5 (Box 79, Folder 5 [39153030525689])
  - Glenny, William (62 pp.), 1995 June 26; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Glenny/Box79:6 (Box 79, Folder 6 [39153030525697])
  - Isserman, Manfred A. (59 pp.), 1995 June 21; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Isserman/Box79:8 (Box 79, Folder 8 [39153030525713])
  - Jackson, William (32 pp.), 1995 July 17; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Jackson/Box79:9 (Box 79, Folder 9 [39153030525721])
  - Kiley, Dan (69 pp.), 1995 August 12; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Kiley/Box79:10 (Box 79, Folder 10 [39153030525739])
  - King, Henry (25 pp.), 1995 October 16; 1984-0025/Witnesses/King_H/Box79:12 (Box 79, Folder 12 [39153030525754])
  - King, Robert (43 pp.), 1995 November 9; 1984-0025/Witnesses/King_R/Box79:11 (Box 79, Folder 11 [39153030525747])
  - Krevit, George (46 pp.), 1995 November 6; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Krevit/Box79:13 (Box 79, Folder 13 [39153030525762])
  - Logan, Andy (40 pp.), 1995 July 18; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Logan/Box79:14 (Box 79, Folder 14 [39153030525770])
  - Maier, Joseph (39 pp.), 1995 July 27; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Maier/Box79:15 (Box 79, Folder 15 [39153030525788])
  - McGee, Palmer S. (35 pp.), 1995 August 24; 1984-0025/Witnesses/McGee/Box79:16 (Box 79, Folder 16 [39153030525796])
  - McMahon, Jr., Raymond J. (34 pp.), 1995 July 21; 1984-0025/Witnesses/McMahon/Box79:17 (Box 79, Folder 17 [39153030525804])
  - Peyser, Seymour (47 pp.), 1995 June 15; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Peyser/Box79:18 (Box 79, Folder 18 [39153030525812])
  - Rettig, Edwin A. (39 pp.), 1995 November 10; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Rettig/Box79:19 (Box 79, Folder 19 [39153030525820])
  - Smith, Howard K. (52 pp.), 1996 August 1; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Smith_H/Box79:20 (Box 80, Folder 20 [39153030525838])
  - Smith, Richard (48 pp.), 1995 August 28; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Smith_R/Box79:21 (Box 80, Folder 21 [39153030525846])
  - Sprecher, Drexel A. (39 pp.), 1995 October 17; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Sprecher/Box79:22 (Box 80, Folder 22 [39153030525853])
  - Wechsler, Herbert (30 pp.), 1995 July 18; 1984-0025/Witnesses/Wechsler/Box79:23 (Box 80, Folder 23 [39153030525861])
- Women And The Connecticut Bar, undated
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Bruce M. Stave.]
  - Catherine G. Roraback (101 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_2d66fe9a2632249a411dbc4706562a09)
- Women In The Connecticut Legislature: Past And Present, 1996-1997
  - unspecified
    [Interviews By: Lisbeth Dizney. This project consists of transcripts only.]
  - Susan Barrett (8 pp.)
  - Julie Belaga (6 pp.)
  - Susan Bysiewicz (5 pp.)
  - Thomasina Clemons (6 pp.)
  - Jackie Cocco (6 pp.)
  - Ann Dandrow (4 pp.)
  - Jackie Durrell (12 pp.)
  - Mary Eberle (4 pp.)
  - Ruth Fahrbach (4 pp.)
  - Jeanne Garvey (4 pp.)
  - Sonya Googins "Sonny" (5 pp.)
  - Elaine Hammers (8 pp.)
  - Denise Merrill (28 pp.)
  - Alice Meyers (7 pp.)
  - Dorothy Miller (8 pp.)
  - Dolly Powers (10 pp.)
  - Jodi Rell (5 pp.)
  - Pamela Sawyer (12 pp.)
  - Angelina Scarpetti "Lee" (5 pp.)
  - Elinor Wilber (9 pp.)
  - unspecified (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_0d288f3f3d7d6108394048522fe9bce9)
- Women's Center (UConn) Oral History Project, 1997 (Box 60)
  - unspecified
    [Project Director: Barbara Cervera and Susan Smith. Interviews By: Barbara Cervera and Susan Smith. This project contains only tapes, no transcripts.]
  - Betty Roper (23 pp.)
  - Gail Shea (38 pp.)
  - Susan Weldon (31 pp.)
  - (Box not specified, Folder data_value_missing_dc9f0772ee77a3bf78da0ccf22c8ada2)